{
  "extraDescription": "NB: one operand is in 8-9 and other operand is in 0-9",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 3",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 2",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 9",
      "answer": "45"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 9",
      "answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 7",
      "answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 1",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 9",
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 9",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 9",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 9",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 8",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 8",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 4",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 9",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 8",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 6",
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 8",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 1",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 7",
      "answer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 8",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 6",
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 5",
      "answer": "45"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 8",
      "answer": "32"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 8",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 5",
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 9",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 8",
      "answer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 3",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 2",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 4",
      "answer": "32"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 9",
      "answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 8",
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 9",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 8",
      "answer": "40"
    }
  ]
}
